Guide to the Rice University Student Association records, 1918-2013 UA 252
Woodson Research Center, Rice University, Houston, Texas
- Series XVII: Addenda 2020
  - Rice Student Volunteer Program (RSVP), 1986-2000
    - Sub-Series A: Photographs of Volunteering Activities, 1996-1999 (Box 30, Folder 4)
      - Outreach Day: Urban Harvest Community Garden, 1997
      - Project Pumpkin, Fall, 1997
      - Unlabeled, ca. 1997
      - American Red Cross: Bowling, 1998
      - Center for the Retarded: Softball & Ceramics, 1998
      - Friends of Hermann Park: Wetlands, 1998
      - Habitat for Humanity, 1998
      - Outreach Day, 1998-10-10
      - Project Pumpkin, 1998
      - RSVP Student Faire Table, 1998
      - Star of Hope: Transitional Living Center for Women & Families, 1998
      - Center for the Retarded: Softball, 1999
      - Outreach Day: The Children's Museum of Houston, Spring, 1999
      - RSVP Changeover Talent Show, 1999
      - Unlabeled, 1999
      - RSVP Group Shots, n.d.
    - Press, 1988-1990 (Box 30, Folder 5)